<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Taubin Drinks dot Beer</title>
    <link>https://taubindrinks.beer/categories/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Taubin Drinks dot Beer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>admin@taubindrinks.beer (Dustin Plunkett)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>admin@taubindrinks.beer (Dustin Plunkett)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://taubindrinks.beer/categories/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog changes</title>
      <link>https://taubindrinks.beer/post/2017-06-22-blog-change/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>admin@taubindrinks.beer (Dustin Plunkett)</author>
      <guid>https://taubindrinks.beer/post/2017-06-22-blog-change/</guid>
      <description>Blog changes I&amp;rsquo;m making some changes to the blog, and moving it from wordpress to Hugo. There are many techinical reasons for this, which I will get to on my personal blog
In the meantime, I need to change the posts so they are able to be posted properly in markdown format.
The old posts and pages will be back, I promise. I will get them up as soon as I can, in the meantime if you have any questions or are looking for any of the old recipes, please email me at taubin at taubindrinks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HBW – Rest in Peace Paul Wicksteed (Time4Another1)</title>
      <link>https://taubindrinks.beer/time4another1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2015 02:33:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>admin@taubindrinks.beer (Dustin Plunkett)</author>
      <guid>https://taubindrinks.beer/time4another1/</guid>
      <description>This week, the homebrewing community lost a prominent member. Paul Wicksteed, know by a lot of people as Time4Another1 passed away. Paul&amp;rsquo;s passing has been very shocking for all of us. My thoughts and prayers go out to Paul&amp;rsquo;s family and friends. The wounds will heal, even if they never go away. I hope wherever Paul is, the beer is some of the best he&amp;rsquo;s ever had. Rest in Peace friend, for now, it&amp;rsquo;s Time4Another1 in your honor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HBW April 15 2015</title>
      <link>https://taubindrinks.beer/hbw-april-15-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2015 07:32:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>admin@taubindrinks.beer (Dustin Plunkett)</author>
      <guid>https://taubindrinks.beer/hbw-april-15-2015/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;#8217;s Wednesday, and that means, Home Brew Wednesday! In this HBW episode, I talk about my latest (as of yet un-named) beer, the Vanilla Java Stout, as well as a couple of the things that didn&amp;#8217;t go entirely right with brewing this time around. Hold on to your shoelaces, it&amp;#8217;s HBW for April 15th. Cheers!
{{ &amp;lt; youtube CbRyScMNPCg &amp;gt;}}</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>